All right I'm Jaden with Luxon and I'm
actually here with my client Josh and
Jonathan they're absolute killer of clients and
I'm just gonna ask them about the
experience of working with me and why
they chose me so why what's the
experience been and why did you guys
choose me so the main thing is
you're hustling your work I think you
truly got to know us got to
know our vision you were always involved very
communicative you talked a lot you asked what what can we
do better how can we improve and
somebody that wants to know us wants
to align with our vision you can't
say no to that what about you for
me it has to be that how easy
it is to work with you because
a lot of times we were really busy and
having somebody that's very flexible in their
schedule that's easy to work with really
makes a big difference And that's my entire
goal you know with for my clients
making sure they're the most successful and
making sure it's it's just convenient I
mean at the end of the day
these are business owners they're running entire
businesses and then we got the time
to you know just being doing all
that extra stuff and that's my job
so I just wanna thank you guys for you
know trusting in me and working with
me and you know you guys are
absolute beast that's all I gotta say
appreciate it